<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<formulario><nombre>Ronald Salazar</nombre><asunto/><email>profitcourse@nowbusiness.info</email><mensaje>Hi jocarsa.com,&#13;
&#13;
You've no-doubt heard about the success of Udemy and other eLearning platforms like it.&#13;
&#13;
Last year Udemy alone did in the range of $600-700 Million, and the industry as a whole is around $400 Billion.&#13;
&#13;
But here's a dirty little secret about the business: Udemy isn't even making profits yet.&#13;
&#13;
OK, technically it's not a secret since they're a publicly-held company, but most of their instructors and customers are certainly not aware of it.&#13;
&#13;
Along with their competitors in the industry, they're focused on growth, and as a result they're losing tens of millions of dollars every quarter.&#13;
&#13;
That's not to say that it's a bad business, or won't become profitable.&#13;
&#13;
However, I bring this up to make two points:&#13;
&#13;
1) There's a better way for most of us to start an eLearning business.&#13;
&#13;
2) You really can compete with platforms like Udemy.&#13;
&#13;
Here's a brand new AI solution that allowed you to start your own Udemy-like academies in a matter of minutes: https://www.nowbusiness.info/profitcourse &#13;
&#13;
While companies like Udemy are building their business like a typical startup in the world of Fortune 500 companies (raising gazillions from investors, taking years to become profitable, etc.), individual entrepreneurs can create a profitable business immediately.&#13;
&#13;
No red tape to cut through.   No investors to keep happy and pay back.   You can start for pennies and be profitable from day one.&#13;
&#13;
In that sense, you REALLY can compete with platforms like Udemy.&#13;
&#13;
Using this new AI platform called CourseMateAi, you can also compete with them in other ways.&#13;
&#13;
By harnessing the power of AI, you can generate new courses on any topic, at any time.&#13;
&#13;
That gives you an edge over those other platforms.   Suppose there is a new trend or breakthrough in a niche.   You can create a course with the AI and launch it within minutes, while instructors on Udemy are scrambling for weeks to do the same.&#13;
&#13;
Again, all this is not to say that the mega-platforms like Udemy and Coursera are bad.   Just to say that you can beat them at their own game by leveraging this new technology today: https://www.nowbusiness.info/profitcourse &#13;
&#13;
Right now CourseMateAi is super affordable during the launch special, but the price will be increasing to a monthly subscription due to huge demand.   Get in now before it's too late.&#13;
&#13;
To your success,&#13;
&#13;
Ronald Salazar&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
UNSUBSCRIBE: https://www.nowbusiness.info/unsubscribe &#13;
Address: 3876 Hilltop Street&#13;
Dalton, MA 01226&#13;
</mensaje></formulario>
